[
  {
    "question": "what did Liverpool vs Burnley play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "4:2",
    "options": [
      "3:3",
      "4:2",
      "0:0",
      "1:4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Chelsea vs Wolverhampton Wanderers play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "1:1",
    "options": [
      "2:4",
      "0:3",
      "3:3",
      "1:1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Arsenal vs Manchester United play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "2:0",
    "options": [
      "4:3",
      "3:1",
      "2:0",
      "1:4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Celta de Vigo vs Real Betis play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "0:1",
    "options": [
      "4:0",
      "0:1",
      "4:3",
      "2:4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Girona vs Valencia play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "2:3",
    "options": [
      "3:0",
      "2:3",
      "0:4",
      "1:0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Levante vs Villarreal play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "0:2",
    "options": [
      "1:3",
      "2:3",
      "1:3",
      "0:2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Sevilla vs Real Sociedad play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "5:2",
    "options": [
      "5:2",
      "0:0",
      "3:3",
      "2:0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Real Valladolid vs Real Madrid play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "1:4",
    "options": [
      "2:1",
      "1:4",
      "2:1",
      "4:3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Bologna vs Cagliari play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "2:0",
    "options": [
      "3:1",
      "3:2",
      "2:0",
      "4:3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Frosinone vs Torino play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "1:2",
    "options": [
      "1:2",
      "2:1",
      "3:0",
      "0:1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Internazionale vs SPAL play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "2:0",
    "options": [
      "1:1",
      "4:2",
      "0:2",
      "2:0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Sampdoria vs Atalanta play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "1:2",
    "options": [
      "3:4",
      "2:1",
      "1:2",
      "0:1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Sassuolo vs Napoli play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "1:1",
    "options": [
      "1:1",
      "3:3",
      "3:3",
      "3:2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Fiorentina vs Lazio play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "1:1",
    "options": [
      "0:2",
      "4:4",
      "0:0",
      "1:1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Hoffenheim vs Nürnberg play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "2:1",
    "options": [
      "4:2",
      "0:2",
      "2:1",
      "4:4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Hannover 96 vs Bayer Leverkusen play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "2:3",
    "options": [
      "3:0",
      "2:3",
      "0:0",
      "1:1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Montpellier vs Angers SCO play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "2:2",
    "options": [
      "0:0",
      "0:1",
      "1:1",
      "2:2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Saint-Étienne vs Lille play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "0:1",
    "options": [
      "4:4",
      "1:3",
      "3:2",
      "0:1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Toulouse vs Guingamp play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "1:0",
    "options": [
      "3:2",
      "4:2",
      "1:0",
      "0:3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Rennes vs Caen play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "3:1",
    "options": [
      "0:4",
      "2:0",
      "3:1",
      "4:2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Olympique Marseille vs Nice play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "1:0",
    "options": [
      "0:3",
      "3:4",
      "1:0",
      "3:3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "what did Birmingham City vs Aston Villa play on 10 March 2019",
    "answer": "0:1",
    "options": [
      "3:3",
      "1:0",
      "0:1",
      "1:0"
    ]
  }
]